<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft &amp;quot;Project Siena&amp;quot; on blog.daruyanagi.jp</title>
    <link>https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/tags/microsoft-quotproject-sienaquot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft &amp;quot;Project Siena&amp;quot; on blog.daruyanagi.jp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 12:04:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/tags/microsoft-quotproject-sienaquot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>付箋タイル 1.2.5.3、Latermark 2.6.0.0、Microsoft &amp;quot;Project Siena&amp;quot; 1.1.0.155、Aristea 0.9.3.4</title>
      <link>https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/entry/2014/03/26/120458/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 12:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/entry/2014/03/26/120458/</guid>
      <description>br/&amp;gt;
### 付箋タイル 1.2.5.3  br/&amp;gt;
&amp;gt;&amp;amp;lt;1.2.5&amp;gt; タイルの黒の枠線を無くしました。
Windows ストア の Windows 用 付箋タイル アプリ### Latermark 2.6.0.0  br/&amp;gt;
&amp;gt;v2.6 enable Settings/Permissions/Notifications for unobtrusive error messages which do not block the UI multi-edit, select &amp;ldquo;Edit Lists&amp;rdquo; from bottom appbar right click (or hold on touch device) on item for edit without viewing article share selected text from Latermark to e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft &amp;quot;Project Siena&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/entry/2013/12/20/072151/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 07:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.daruyanagi.jp/entry/2013/12/20/072151/</guid>
      <description>br/&amp;gt;
Microsoft Project Siena (Beta)なんかすんごいのぶっこんできたなー。&amp;gt;Microsoft Project Siena (code name) is the beta release of a new technology for business experts, business analysts, consultants and other app imagineers. Now, without any programming, you can create powerful apps for the device-first and cloud-connected world, with the potential to transform today’s business processes.  Apps to explore media-rich product catalogs and create ensembles that together serve a customer’s needs Apps used on the spot to resolve customer service bottlenecks and logistics exceptions, with the custom intelligence to help the user make local trade-offs Apps for auditing and inspecting a manufacturing facility through photos, videos and pen and voice notes, all tied to an asset database Siena apps are as easy as editing a document.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>